Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- H, Series VIII
  - Health Services
    - Health Services Projects: History and Statistics
      - Historical notes made from annual plans and reports with statistical charts: H-02.07.01/0001 - H-02.07.01/0006 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
        Including regarding: Time investment; Okhaldhunga: hospital, community health; Gorkha: hospital, community health; Lalitpur: community health; Palpa: hospital, community health; Bhaktapur: hospital and CH combined
    - Commission on Institutional Implications in Health Care
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.08.01/0001 - H-02.08.01/0013, 1979 Nov- 1980 May (Box 78, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: CMC evaluation of health projects of UMN; Report from CMC; Seminar on "Rising Hospital costs - Whose responsibility?"; Meeting minutes; How to limit rising costs, UMN subsidies, etc.
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.08.01/0014 - H-02.08.01/0022, 1980 Sep- 1981 Mar (Box 78, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Input from UMN physicians; Input from Board appointees; Findings and recommendations of study of cost control; Appropriate health care; Final report of Commission and 2 copies
    - The Way Ahead and LTP Planning
      - The Way Ahead and LTP Planning 85/86: H-02.09.01/0001 - H-02.09.01/0006, 1985 -1986 May (Box 78, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: The Way Ahead: 1985-1990. A working paper; Staffing projections; Many individual and project responses; Workers' conference discussion groups, questions and reports
    - Hospital Sustainability
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.10.01/0001 - H-02.10.01/0012, 1982 Aug- 1992 Jan (Box 77, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Sustainability of health projects; Health financing and cost recovery in Nepal; Budget subsides and correspondence with Nepal; Proposal hospital subsidy levels; Hospital economics; Proposal for hospital subsidy percentages; Report of South Asia hospital survey done in 1990
      - Reports, etc.: Health financing and cost recovery in Nepal: H-02.10.01/0002, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.10.01/0013 - H-02.10.01/0026, 1992- 1997 Oct (Box 77, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Study on financing with statistics; Letter from Tansen on MAF; Thoughts on endowment planning; Letters from Gorkha on sustainability; Thoughts on endowment planning; Feasibility and fundraising development study; Hospitals towards the future policy principles
      - Reports, etc.: Feasibility and Fundraising Development Study: H-02.10.01/0020, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - TB and Leprosy Workshops
      - Papers; Workshop agenda: H-02.11.01, 1983 Mar 7-9 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Nepal Christian Hospitals Association
      - Reports, etc.: General: H-02.12.01/0001 - H-02.12.01/0012, 1995 Jul- 1999 Dec (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Reports, etc.: (H-02.12), 1995-2001 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals future: general
      - Plans, reports, etc.: (H-02.13), 2000-2006 (Box 203, Folder 2-5)
    - Hospitals Steering / Management / Governing Committee
      - Minutes: (H-02.14), 2001-2006 (Box 203, Folder 6-7)
    - Hospitals future: correspondence
      - Correspondence: (H-02.15) - RESTRICTED, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals Consultancies
      - Reports, evaluations on government hospitals (D. Harding): (H-02.16), 1999-2000 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Health Services Office
    - Open House Clinic
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.01.01/0001 - H-03.01.01/0020 - RESTRICTED, 1983- 1999 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Dental Program/ Oral Health Program
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.02.01/0001 - H-03.02.01/0031, 1975 Apr-1989 Sep (Box 79, Folder 11)
        Including regarding: Plan for Oral Health Survey; Review and proposals; Outline plans for program; Correspondence and some reports; Need for Advisory Committee; Dental Advisory Group (DAG) minutes; Dental health in Nepal
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.02.01/0032 - H-03.02.01/0062, 1989 Nov- 1994 Aug (Box 79, Folder 12)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; OHP minutes; Annual reports; Proposal for dental services for UMN personnel; Dentistry in Nepal; Mission statement
      - Reports, etc. - Health of the Month 1987-1993: H-03.02.01/0046 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.02.01/0063 - H-03.02.01/0080, 1994 Aug- 1997 Feb (Box 80, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: OH Newsletters; Funding proposal; Description of program; Agreement for village based training; Promotion of life styles conducive to oral health; PMC minutes; Annual reports, and plans; Advisory group meeting
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.02.01/0081 - H-03.02.01/0096, 1997-1999 Dec (Box 80, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Annual reports, and plans; Oral Health Dental Therapist Project; Advisory group minutes; Leaflet and poster
      - Oral Health Program reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.02), 1995-2008 (Box 202, Folder 3-7)
      - Oral Health Program leaflet (H-03.02), n.d. (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Institute of Medicine
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.03.01/0001 - H-03.03.01/0010, 1975 Jan- 1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Correspondence regarding bonding nurses and assignments; Proposed curriculum for HA training; Details of AHW practical work courses; IOM scholarships; Community medicine course
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.03.01/0011 - H-03.03.01/0024, 1981- 1990 Oct (Box 80, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: List of CMA course books; Strike and disruption on campuses; Suggestion of Nursing School in Tansen; Estimate of Five-year man power needs; Seconded workers' plans and reports
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.03.01/0025 - H-03.03.01/0032, 1991 Feb (Box 80, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: List of courses run by IOM; Annual reports; Plan for community and clinical experience and management theory classes for MBBS; "Clinical and Community Experiences" for IOM students and program in AP, Gorkha
      - Secondment, physiotherapy, etc.: (H-03.03), 2003 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health Program / Centre for Mental Health and Counselling (CMC)
      - Reports, etc: H-03.04.01/0001 - H-03.04.01/0059, 1983 Jan- 1990 Mar (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
        Including regarding: Beginning discussions on drug abuse prevention: Initial planning meeting for psychiatric project; Draft plans and record of minutes; MHAG minutes; Annual reports and plans; Leaflet on drugs
      - Reports, etc. - Manual of MH training for CHWB: H-03.04.01/0039, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc. - Manual of MH training for CHWB - Nepali: H-03.04.01/0040, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc. - Manual of MH training for CHWB: H-03.04.01/0041, 1990 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc. - Report of Drug Use Survey: H-03.04.01/0045, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc: H-03.04.01/0060 - H-03.04.01/0112, 1990- 1995 (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
        Including regarding: MHAG minutes; Mental health patients in PMC services in Nepal; PMC minutes; Proposal for support of activities at Youth Vision; Statements from NGO reps; Project progress report
      - Reports, etc. - Five Years of Community CH Services - an evaluation report: H-03.04.01/0081, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc: H-03.04.02/0001 - H-03.04.02/0058, 1995-1999 (Box 81, Folder 4-7)
        Including regarding: Report to TF; Annual plans and reports; Team meeting minutes; MHAG minutes; Brief description of MHP; PMC minutes
      - Mental Health Program reports, plans: (H-03.04), 1997-2003 (Box 205, Folder 1-2)
      - Mental Health Program leaflet (H-03.04), n.d. (Box 252, Folder 7)
      - CMC General, reports, plans: (H-03.04), 2004-2006 (Box 205, Folder 3-4)
    - Nutrition Programme / Nutrition Promotion and Consultancy Services (NPCS)
      For nutrition material see –03.00.01
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.05.01/0001 - H-03.05.01/0050, 1969 -1995 (Box 81, Folder 8-10)
        Including regarding: Meals for Millions- Multipurpose food distribution; Food services in hospitals in Nepal; Annual reports; Third Asian Congress on Nutrition; Nutrition PMC; Summary of nutrition history for UMN 35th booklet; Nutrition seminar; PMC, minutes; Orientation/planning workshop
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.05.01/0051 - H-03.05.01/0073, 1996-1999 (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
        Including regarding: Leaflet; Vitamin A posters and details; PMC; Annual reports; Strategic Plan; PMC meeting; Nutrition baseline surveys and comments on methodology; Proposal for expansion in underserved districts; District training program
      - Reports, etc.: Annual Report: H-03.05.01/0063, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Reports,etc.: H-03.05.02/0001 - H-03.05.02/0018, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Bulletins; Audits; Annual report; Summary progress report; UMN Nutrition Programme strategic plan 2000-2004
      - Nutrition Programme reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.05), 1997-2002 (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - Nutrition Programme reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.05), 2003 (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - NPCS reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.05), 2004-2007 (Box 206, Folder 2-4)
      - Nutrition Bulletin, Year 7, Issue 1, 2004 (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - Administration
      - Minutes, reports: H-03.06.01/0001 - H-03.06.01/0025 - RESTRICTED, 1973-1999 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - Medical Library, HQ/ MSP: Central Library
      - Correspondence with donors: CMF, WCC, Correspondence regarding HELLIS network; New accessions; New additions and slide sets: H-03.07.01/0001 - H-03.07.01/0022, 1975 -1994 (Box 79, Folder 3-4)
    - Medical Supplies Department /Medical Services Management Trust
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.08.01/0001 - H-03.08.01/0087 - RESTRICTED, 1968- 1996 (Box 82, Folder 4,7,8,9)
      - Health Services Office: Medical Supplies Department (formerly "Drug Store"): H-03.08.01/0020 - H-03.08.01/0035, 1986 Feb- 1987 Oct (Box 82, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Legal aspects of drug regulations; Annual plan and report; PAG minutes
      - Health Services Office: Medical Supplies Department (formerly "Drug Store"): H-03.08.01/0036 - H-03.08.01/0053, 1987 Nov- 1990 Jan (Box 82, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Statement of operation policy; Correspondence regarding import of drugs; PAG minutes and MSD Management Advisory Committee minutes; MAC and PAG minutes; Director's report; Customer survey
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.08.02/0001 - H-03.08.02/0017 - RESTRICTED, 1995- 1999 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - MSD reports, plans, etc.; incident report: (H-03.08) - RESTRICTED, 1999-2003 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - MSD/ MSMT reports, plans, etc; tendering process: (H-03.08) - RESTRICTED, 2004-2005 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Maintenance
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.09.01/0001 - H-03.09.01/0038, 1969-1996 (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
        Including regarding: Query about training at BTI; Outline of training scheme; BTI participation; Guidelines for pool of maintenance workers; Quality standards and training; One day workshop
      - Maintenance manual: H-03.09.01/0013, ca. 1980 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Training and Manpower
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.10.01/0001 - H-03.10.01/0015, 1986 Jan- 1990 (Box 78, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Plans for 1986/1987; Annual reports; Annual plan; Division of office into training and manpower section
    - Planning Information and Evaluation
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.11.01/0001 - H-03.11.01/0034, 1986 Feb- 1991 Aug (Box 78, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Statistics section, plans for 1986/87; Minutes; Reports; Minutes; Outline of PIE work; Planning, Monitoring, Evaluation and Management Information Support (PME and MIS) Program proposal, Draft 5
    - National TB Control Programme / TB Net Support Project
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.12.01/0001 - H-03.12.01/0030, 1983- 2000 (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
        Including regarding: National TB Control Program in Nepal; Notes on UMN TB Control proposal; Summary annual report; Workshop on community based care of people with HIV and tuberculosis.
      - DOTS reports, etc.: (H-03.12), 2001 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - HIV / AIDS Program, Sakriya / Sakriya Sewa Samaj
      - Reports,etc.: H-03.13.01/0000 - H-03.13.01/0010, 1992 Dec- 1996 Jun (Box 79, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Tansen policy on blood donation and HIV testing; Workshop for AGNW objections and activities; Coordinator's monthly report; Objectives for HIV/ AIDs Coordinator; Policy discussion document
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.13.01/0011 - H-03.13.01/0027, 1996- 1998 Oct (Box 79, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: The potential impact of HIV/ AIDs on our hospitals: discussion paper; World AIDs Day 1996; Report of visit to Tansen; Overview; Revised mission and vision statement
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.13.01/0028 - H-03.13.01/0042, 1998 Nov- 2000 Jan (Box 79, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Advocacy, UMN and use of media; Summary and detailed annual reports; Cumulative HIV/AIDs situation in Nepal; Evaluation of Sakriya Program
      - Sakriya Unit reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.13), 1999-2004 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Sakriya Sewa Samaj reports, plans, etc.: (H-03.13), 2005-2007 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Share and Care
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.14.01/0001 - H-03.14.01/0006, 1996 -1999 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Family Planning and Safe Motherhood:
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.15.01/0001 - H-03.15.01/0014, 1996-2000 Jan (Box 76, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Safe Motherhood (SM) Awareness event; SM memorial march The Nepal SM project (NSM); SM network AGM; How can motherhood be made safer in Nepal?; Reproductive Health (RH) annual report, 1999
    - Rehabilitation Program
      - Reports, etc.: H-03.16.01/0001 - H-03.16.01/0005, 1998 Sep- 1999 (Box 76, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Review of first year, 1997/98; Update, plans for 1999/2000; Annual Report, 1998/99; Rehab. Fund for children with physical disability; Disability in Nepal
      - Reports, etc.: (H-03.16), 2001-2004 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - B. P. Koirala Institute of Health Sciences, Dharan: General
      - Reports, secondment agreements, etc.: (H-03.17), 1999-2006 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - B. P. Koirala Institute of Health Sciences, Dharan: Correspondence
      - Correspondence: (H-03.18) - RESTRICTED, 2005 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Reproductive Health
      - General: (H-03.19), 2002-2003 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights
    - Correspondence, etc.: H-04.00.01/0001 - H-04.00.01/0007 - RESTRICTED, 1985- 1995 Aug (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Hydro Consult (P) Ltd.
    Continued from B-08.06, independent company not based in Butwal
    - Reports: (H-05.01), 2000-2004 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Board and AGM minutes: (H-05.02), 1999-2002, 2004-2005 (Box 208, Folder 1-2)
  - Human Development and Community Services (HDCS)
    - Reports, etc.: (H-06.01), 1999-2005 (Box 208, Folder 3)
- I, Series IX
  - Information requests
    - Correspondence: I-01.00.01, 1953-1989 (Box 83, Folder 2-4)
  - Income Tax
    - Correspondence, etc.: I-02.00.01/0001 - I-02.00.01/0012 - RESTRICTED, 1970 Feb- 1995 Jun (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Imports
    - Imports: I-03.00.01/0001 - I-03.00.01/0021 - RESTRICTED, 1955-1994 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
      Including regarding: Request regarding exemption for hospital supplies, agriculture equipment, etc.
  - Inter-Mission Business Office
    - Correspondence, etc.: I-04.00.01 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - International Assistance Mission
    - Correspondence, etc.: I-05.00.01 - RESTRICTED (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Interserve/ BMMF:
    - Correspondence: I-06.00.01, 1954 -1997 (Box 84, Folder 4-6)
  - I.C.C.O, Holland
    - Correspondence: I-07.00.01 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - International Christian University Church, Japan
    - Correspondence: I-08.00.01 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - International Missionary Council
    - Correspondence: I-09.00.01 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - International Nepal Fellowship (Nepal Evangelistic Band)
    - Reports, correspondence, agreements, etc.: I-10.00.01/0001 - I-10.00.01/0048 - RESTRICTED, 1954-1999 (Box 83, Folder 5-8)
- J, Series X
  - Jumala Project and KCST
    - Reports
      - Reports: J-01.01.01/2/3 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.01/0001- J-01.01.01/0011, 1977 Mar- 1978 Jun (Box 84, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Report of visit to Jumla; Proposed education work in Far Western Region; Information regarding Peace Corps and SADP; Papers preparing for survey; Committee meeting and various notes
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.01/0012- J-01.01.01/0021, 1978 Oct- 1979 May (Box 84, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Proposal for Rural Trade Training School; Jumla Project Planning Committee minutes; Report on Jumla Project
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.01/0022- J-01.01.01/0044, 1979 May- 1981 Apr (Box 84, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Write up about JTS; Proposed operational draft; Report from nutritionist; Letter to BFW about JTS policies; First KTS report; Quarterly reports
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.01/0045- J-01.01.01/0058, 1981 Apr- 1982 Jul (Box 84, Folder 11)
        Including regarding: Quarterly reports; Radio communication; Food situation in Jumala; Major problems of food and staff
      - Reports, etc.: J-01.01.01 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.02/0001- J-01.01.02/0015, 1982 Oct- 1983 Jul (Box 85, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Financial emergency: circular to member bodies; Reports; Funding application; Guidelines for charters; PMC minutes; Report of nutritionist's visit; Detailed reports of food situation, etc.
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.02/0016- J-01.01.02/0022, 1983 Sep- 1984 Mar (Box 85, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Details of construction course; Reports; King's visit; Student training and staff appointment
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.02/0023- J-01.01.02/0039, 1984 Apr- 1984 Jul (Box 85, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Discussion on health work; Materials development; Short evaluation; Working in formal education as an HMG employee; KTS procurement of equipment and supplies; Leave guidelines for expatriates; Reports
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.02/0040- J-01.01.02/0057, 1984 Aug- 1985 Apr (Box 85, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Reduction of HMG budget; Five year planning notes; Notes from TVED meetings; Letter on budget details; Notes on health program; Regarding tax letters; Concerns regarding transportation, finances and jobs for graduates
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.03/0001- J-01.01.03/0009, 1985 Apr- Jul (Box 85, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Instructor training for technical schools; Report on RDC trip; Report of NFE visit; Sending school teachers to local schools; Regarding vaccines; UMN's involvement in KTS
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.03/0010- J-01.01.03/0016, 1985 Sep- 1986 Jan (Box 85, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Report on KTS for CTEVT principals' seminar; PMC minutes and appendices; Negotiations regarding teachers in schools; Discussion regarding health plans; Future health care involvement in Jumla; prospects and proposals
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.03/0017- J-01.01.03/0029, 1986 Jan- Jul (Box 85, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Assignments for primary school teachers; Staff training needs; PMC minutes; Dental visit report; HMG budget cuts; Jet boat transportation: Animal health visit report
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.03/0030- J-01.01.03/0037, 1986 Jul- 1986 Nov (Box 85, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Forestry LTP budget revision for 1986/87; Eye campus; PMC minutes; Report on sawmill; KTS Co-Principal work load
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.04/0001- J-01.01.04/0016, 1987 Jan- Sep (Box 86, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: KTS campus staff housing: long term view; Forestry LTP; JUMP work commitments; PMC minutes; Oral health problems survey; Forestry LTP discussion; Forestry annual report
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.04/0017- J-01.01.04/0029, 1987 Oct- 1988 May (Box 86, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Forestry visit report and recommendations; Numbers of students in KTS; Meeting with health personnel; Agriculture report; Dental program in Jumla; Correspondence on radio link
      - General English Years 1,2,3 KTS:J-01.01.04/0022 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - KTS Management information: J-01.01.04/0023 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.04/0030- J-01.01.04/0043, 1988 Jun- 1989 Mar (Box 86, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Report of forestry visit; Correspondence on planning of forestry program; RDC visit report; PMC minutes; Proposal for improvement in construction course; Visit of King and Queen
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.04/0044- J-01.01.04/0059, 1989 Mar- Dec (Box 86, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Renewal of JUMP agreement, etc., and response; Funding application; PMC minutes; JUMP administration structure; Report of administrative visit
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.05/0001- J-01.01.05/0020, 1990 Jan- 1991 May (Box 86, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Guesthouse leaflet; Funding application summary; PMC minutes; Forestry annual report; Future of sawmill; Correspondence on saw mill future
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.05/0021- J-01.01.05/0041, 1991 May- 1992 Jul (Box 86, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: New KTS agreement with HMG; DCS extension work in Jumla; Project administration chart; PMC minutes; Fuel shortage
      - Publication: Cooking Stoves for the Karhali Zone: J-01.01.05/0033, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.05/0042- J-01.01.05/0055, 1992 Aug- 1993 May (Box 86, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Minutes of initial phase of JUMP Forestry strategic planning meetings; Comments and outline regarding Forestry Program strategic planning; Review of present and future plans and responses; ANM course under CTEVT minute; Proposal to phase out JUMP's input into forest guard training
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.05/0056- J-01.01.05/0076, 1993 Jul- 1994 Dec (Box 86, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Forestry training; Meeting on Community Health work; PMC minutes; Computer use; Forestry management chart; Professional Forestry Group meeting; Agreement for handover of sawmill buildings and carpentry equipment; Agreement with CTEVT
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.06/0001- J-01.01.06/0014, 1995 Feb- Aug (Box 87, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Discussion of Jumla Project: minutes; Project description-detailed; Report of project visit; Short project description; Report of health visit; Closing celebration; One and a half decades of working together: booklet in Nepali; Extended Management Committee minutes
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.06/0015- J-01.01.06/0026, 1995 Oct- 1997 Jan (Box 87, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Area description; KCST extended Management Committee minutes; Village profile; Brief report on out of school children program; Grant application; Preliminary results of Baseline Survey
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.06/0027- J-01.01.06/0047, 1997 Feb- 1998 (Box 87, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Extended Management Committee meeting; Report to Swedish NGOs; PMC meeting; EMC meeting; Jumla Area Description; Reports
      - Reports, etc: J-01.01.06/0048- J-01.01.06/0060, 1998 Jul- 1999 Nov (Box 87, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: KCST leaflet in English and Nepali; Reports and plans; Community Nutrition Project- Inauguration/ Orientation/ Training; Correspondence on proposal for wind power
      - Reports, plans, etc. (closed 2002, Maoist threat): (J-01.01), 1995-2005 (Box 208, Folder 4-5)
      - PMC / IMC minutes: (J-01.01) (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Evaluations
      - Evaluations: J-01.02.01/0001- J-01.02.01/0003, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Role of KTS in preparation of youth for employment: Follow-up study of graduates and employees; Evaluation of Technical Instruction of KTS; Jumla evaluation
    - Maps